http://www.multicultural.com/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
HomeAbout MMR Our TeamTestimonialsMMR in the NewsFAQsWoman-Owned Business CertificationsProducts and Services Public RelationsPress ReleasesPress ReferralsConference & Event ServicesRecruitmentConsulting & ResearchRate sheetMorePublic Relations Our Clients and their PressConsultingContact Us
Welcome to Multicultural Marketing Resources, Inc. (MMR). We are a publisher of newsletters, a consulting firm to corporations seeking information and a marketing firm for multicultural ad agencies seeking visibility and connections. MMR publishes Multicultural Marketing News (MMRNews), an emailed newsletter; The Source Book of Multicultural Experts online and maintains a Speakers Showcase for conferences, ERG events, and corporate meetings. Other services include recruitment consulting, job postings, business introductions and distribution of RFPs. Lisa Skriloff, a consultant and writer on diversity, marketing and travel is President of Multicultural Marketing Resources, Inc. and founded the company in 1994. She is editor of the above mentioned publications as well as Multicultural Travel News. Contact her at lisa@multicultural.com or 212-242-3351.
Your Account
Hello
Subscribe
Join
Sign in
Experts Directory Get ListedFind an ExpertView All ExpertsThe Sourcebook of Multicultural ExpertsQ and A with Featured ExpertAsk an ExpertSpeakers Showcase Get ListedSearch SpeakersView All SpeakersCareer Center Post a JobCurrent Opportunites/Available CandidatesDiversity RecruitmentEvents View All EventsSubmit an EventEvent CoverageUpcoming EventsEvent Planning/Guest ServicesEvent InvitationsMMR News & Articles Multicultural Marketing NewsMulticultural ArticlesMulticultural Arts & Entertainment NewsMulticultural Travel NewsSubmit NewsMMRNews Editorial CalendarSubscribe to MMRNewsEthnic & Niche Markets African AmericanAsian AmericanDisability MarketHispanicAllResources Recommended Multicultural and Diversity BooksDirect MarketingJournalists Seeking ExpertsResearchRFPsThe African American HomeownerTranslationMoreMMR Membership Our MembersQ & A with Featured ExpertQ & A with Featured ExpertCase Studies
Advertise
Privacy Policy
Welcome to the Multicultural Marketing Resources Web site at www.multicultural.com
(the “Site”)! This site is owned by Multicultural Marketing Resources, Inc. ("MMR" or "we"). This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding collection, use and disclosure of personal information that you may provide to us through the Site.
What personal information do we collect on the Site, and how do we collect it? Below we list all the kinds of personal information we ask you for, depending on what you are doing on the Site.
If you register as a Member:
First and last name
E-mail address
Company Name
Job Title (optional)
Phone number
web address
If you subscribe to any aspect of MMRNews:
First and last name
E-mail address
Company name and address
Company phone number
Company web address
If you submit a listing to the Multicultural Experts Directory:
First and last name
Home or work address
E-mail address
Phone number
Company name
Web address
Specialty
Job title (optional)
Organizations (optional)
If you submit a listing to the Source Book of Multicultural Experts:
First and last name
Work address
Phone number
Company name
Job title (optional)
E-mail address
If you are a journalist seeking an expert to respond to a query:
First and last name
Media outlet or organization
Address
Phone Number
E-mail address
If you are seeking to post a press release on the Site:
First and last name
E-mail address
Company
Home address
Web address
Phone number
If you want to buy a book:
First and last name
Shipping address
Billing address
E-mail address
Credit card number, expiration date and security code
How do we use the personal information that we collect? We use the personal information that we collect as follows:
If you provide your e-mail address for any particular purpose, we will use it for that purpose. For example, if you provide your e-mail address in connection with subscribing to MMRNews, we will use that e-mail address to send you
MMRNews newsletters and e-blasts . In addition, we may forward your e-mail address to our e-blast service provider, to use solely to send you e-mail promotional messages for other products and services offered by MMR and by other companies.
If you are a journalist and you provide your e-mail address as a way for experts to contact you in response to a query that you want us to post on the Web Site, then we will post that e-mail address as part of the query.
If you provide your telephone number in connection with providing a listing in the Multicultural Experts Directory or the print Source Book of Multicultural Experts, we will use it to call you when it is time to renew your listing. We also may call you to ask if you want to purchase any other products or services that MMR offers. We may provide your number to a prospective client that calls us to ask for referrals to companies that provide the services that you
provide or to a recruiter who calls us asking for qualified candidates. (If you do not wish us to provide your number for these purposes, please let us know and we will not do so.) If you provide it for any other purpose, we may use it to call you to recommend that you list yourself or your company in the Directory or the Source Book.
If you provide your snail mail address when you order the print Source Book of Multicultural Marketing Experts, we will use it to send you the print volume you ordered. We also may use it to send you informational and promotional mailings from MMR and other companies.
When you provide your credit card number and related information to pay for a listing in the Directory or the Source Book, or buy a book from our store, your credit number is provided to our credit-card processor, to use solely to process your order.
If we sell, assign, or otherwise transfer the business of this Web site to which your personal information relates, we will transfer your personal information to the buyer and use reasonable commercial efforts to require the buyer to agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
If we are required to disclose your personal information by any applicable law, court order, or government regulation, we will comply with such laws, orders or regulations.
Do we use cookies (and what are they)?
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site places on your computer to facilitate and enhance your communication and interaction with that site by making it easier for you to navigate the site. That is how we use cookies on this site. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer. Cookies (and JavaScript) must be enabled for you to enter and use this site.
What about non-confidential information that you transmit to us?
Any communication or material you transmit to us by electronic mail or otherwise, including any data, questions, comments, suggestions, or the like is and will be treated as non-confidential and nonproprietary. We may use anything you transmit to us or post on this Web site for any purpose, including but not limited to, reproduction, disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, posting, and/or ranking.
Furthermore, you expressly agree that we are free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to us without compensation and for any purpose whatsoever, including but not limited to, developing, manufacturing, and marketing products and services using such information.
How can you be sure that your information is secure on our Web site?
We take reasonable steps to protect your information as you transmit it from your computer to our site and to protect your information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever 100% secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on this site, it is your responsibility to safeguard them.
This site may contain links or references to other Web sites in addition to the ones we have already mentioned. Please be aware that we do not control such other Web sites and that, in any case, this Privacy Policy does not apply to those Web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every Web site you visit.
How can you correct your personal information on this site?
You can update any account or profile information at any time or you can
contact us at any time and our staff can assist you with any updates.
How will you know if this policy has changed?
If this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted here. Please check back periodically and especially before you provide any personal information. This Privacy Policy was last updated on September 27, 2010
JOURNALISTS
Find diverse sources and experts on niche markets and diversity
Search for an expert online in Multicultural Experts Directory
Post your query here for experts to respond to
Have your query sent to selected experts we can recommend and set up interviews for you
Promote your diversity initiatives and multicultural marketing campaigns:
Promote your events in our Calendar of Recommended Multicultural and Diversity Events
Disseminate your press releases via MMRNews
Request speakers for events and conferences
Connect with sponsors
Learn more about how MMR works with associations
Multicultural Marketing Resources (MMR)
Lisa Skriloff, President
email: lisa@multicultural.com
General Inquiries: info@multicultural.com
AdvertiseContact UsPrivacy PolicyTerms & ConditionsThe Multicultural Market
